mycen.com.my 2018-10-29

# MALAYSIA CENTRAL: Terms Of Use & Privacy Policy

**  
****Malaysia Central - Terms of Use:** **  
**  
By accessing any page in Malaysia Central (aka MyCen) directly or indirectly, you have already declared, agreed and accepted the following terms which may be updated by us from time to time without notice to you;

The entire editorial, textual, audiio-visual and graphical content of Malaysia Central is protected by Malaysian, national and international copyright laws. This includes the site's "look & feel", concept, features, color combinations, themes, button shapes, graphics, cartoons, pictures, audio files, video files, text files, html files, maps, charts, kmz/kml files, logos, artwork, naming, design, arrangement, layout, words, source codes, javascripts, search results, listings, database, comments, descriptions and all other elements. Any unauthorised copying or use of any material in part or in whole from this site is a violation of applicable criminal and civil laws.

The framing, mirroring, scraping or data-mining of this web site or any of its content in any form and by any method is strictly prohibited. You may however link or deep-link to any page without permission. 

The providers, owners and creators of Malaysia Central are not legally and morally responsible for the accuracy, legality, availability, validity, quality, reliability, safety, fitness, morality, usefulness, merchantability, completeness and consequence of any content made available from or through this site directly or indirectly. 

The providers, owners and creators of Malaysia Central do not endorse, support, sponsor, represent, warrant or guarantee any product, service, claim, transaction, opinion, comment, recommendation, description, suggestion, advice, consultation or information given, offered, hired, exchanged, traded, sold, advertised, announced or implied by any of the external sites, establishments, organisation or entities listed on this site.

All logos, brands and product names referenced on this web site may be the trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners/holders. 

By accessing any page in Malaysia Central, you will have released and discharged the providers, owners and creators of Malaysia Central from any and all liability which might arise.

**Malaysia Central - Privacy Policy: ** Malaysia Central does not collect personally identifiable information about its visitors, except when such visitors provide such information on a voluntary basis. This information is not shared with any third parties. We will at no stage, under any circumstances, give out your e-mail address to anyone, or forward messages to you on behalf of anyone. The e-mail addresses on our database is used to send information updates about this site and you may choose to opt out. There are tracking and monitoring programs installed on this site that records each visitor's movement, usage, referrals, IP address, browser type, operating system and other non-personal information.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

Google uses the DART cookie to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy [**here**](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can find additional information in Appendix A of the [**NAI Self-Regulatory principles for publishers**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/pdfs/NAI_principles.pdf) (PDF). Please note that the NAI may change this sample language at any time.
